A Royal Winter is a tv movie, romance film directed by Ernie Barbarash.
While on a last-minute European holiday, a young woman finds herself in the middle of a real-life
fairy tale when a chance meeting with a handsome local leads to something more.
However, things get complicated when she learns that the "local" is actually a prince who is about to be
crowned King, and whose mother is dead-set against her royal son's romance with the tourist.
Maggie Marks, played by Merritt Patterson.
Prince Adrian of Calpurnia, played by Jack Donnelly.
Queen Beatrice of Calpurnia, played by Samantha Bond.
Sarah Price, played by Rhea Bailey.
Felix Meyers, played by Cian Barry.
Henrik, played by Ryan Ellsworth.
Ariel Winter Workman (born January 28, 1998) is an American actress.
She gained her career breakthrough and stardom in the 2010s for playing the intelligent and nerdy Alex Dunphy in the ABC sitcom Modern Family (2009–2020), for which she and
her several costars won the Screen Actors Guild Award for Outstanding Performance by an Ensemble in a Comedy Series four consecutive times from 2010 to 2013.
Winter made her film debut in Kiss Kiss Bang Bang (2005) at the age of seven, followed by roles in the films
Speed Racer (2008), The Chaperone (2011), Safelight (2015), and The Last Movie Star (2017).
She also voiced roles in the animated films Horton Hears a Who!
(2008), ParaNorman (2012), Mr.
Peabody & Sherman (2014), and Smurfs: The Lost Village (2017); and voiced Carrie Kelley /
Robin in the two part animated film Batman: The Dark Knight Returns (2012–2013).
The film explores themes of prince, europe, playful, relaxed, romantic.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.